Search

Privacy Policy
==============

We are very sensitive to the privacy needs of its website visitors and subscribers and is wholly committed to maintaining privacy at the highest level. We do not sell or otherwise share subscribers’ or website visitors’ personal information with anyone.

To better understand our online privacy policies, please read the following Privacy Policy.

**Subscriber Information**

We never automatically collects any information that specifically identifies you such as your name, address, or e-mail address. This information is collected only when you voluntarily provide it as part of the subscription process (“Subscriber Information”). We will ask you whenever we need Subscriber Information that identifies you or allows us to contact you.

**Consent and Security**

It is your choice whether or not you provide your Subscriber Information to us, but Subscriber Information is required for us to provide you with services (for example, access to this website under a subscription agreement).

**Use of Subscriber Information**

Your Subscriber Information may be used internally within our company. For example, we may use your Subscriber Information internally to provide subscription services to you and process your transactions, to contact you for customer service and billing purposes, to communicate to you about your subscription or changes to our service, to understand who uses the Website and to improve the Website. In addition, we reserve the right to disclose your Subscriber Information under limited circumstances in the event we believe that the Website is being used to commit unlawful acts, and/or if disclosure of your Subscriber Information is required to comply with applicable laws or regulations, or with a court or administrative order.

**Usage Information**

Non-personally identifying information (“Usage Information”) comprises information that does not identify any particular user. Examples include: information about which of our pages are visited on an aggregate level, browser type, operating system type, or IP address.

**Use of Usage Information**

Your Usage Information may be disclosed internally within our company and to third parties. For example, we may disclose Usage Information in order to better understand which parts of the Website users are visiting, to improve the content of the Website, and for marketing, advertising, or research purposes. (Institutional licensees should refer to their subscription and license agreement).

**Cookies**

The Website may place a text file called a “cookie” in the browser files of your computer. Cookies can be used to provide you with tailored information from the Website. The cookie itself does not contain Subscriber Information. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it.

**Effective Date**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of October 27, 2007 and will remain in effect unless changed. we may modify this Privacy Policy at any time, and such modifications shall be effective immediately upon posting of the modified Privacy Policy on the Website.

**Contacting the Website**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Website, or your dealings with this Website, please contact us using our contact us page.

Copyright explorepanel.com 2024. All rights reserved.
